filepicker.io 2019-03-04

# Privacy Policy Regarding Information

This Privacy Policy describes how Filestack, Inc. (“Filestack,” “we” or “our”) collects information from and about you as a visitor to our website (the”Site”), how we use that information, and the circumstances under which we share information with others.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to personal data that you transmit as a Filestack customer to establish and maintain your account, or to any personal data that may be part of the content that you submit or manage using the Filestack service. The Terms of Use for our services describe our obligations with respect to any personal data that you submit in connection with your services account or as part of your content.

 **Not for Children.**  None of our websites, applications or services are intended for children. Please do not submit information about yourself using our websites if you are under 13. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 13 who may have submitted information to us please contact us at [privacy@filestack.com](mailto:privacy@filestack.com).

Please contact us at [privacy@filestack.com](mailto:privacy@filestack.com) (i) you wish to find out more about our use and disclosure of your personal data and how to limit it, (ii) you wish to exercise your right to access, amend, or delete any personal data we hold about you; or (iii) you have any other questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy.

### What information do we collect?

 **Webserver.**  
When you visit the Site as a guest, our web server will capture your IP address, the time and duration of your visit, and the pages on the Site that you visit. It may also collect information about your browser, device (including your mobile device), location and other information of the type collected by web servers generally. We use cookies, web beacons, and other techniques to identify your browser and device to your guest activity on the Site. Please see the section below captioned “Online Data Collection Technologies” for more information regarding our use of these techniques and your ability to restrict our collection of data in this manner.

 **Analytics Tools.**  
We may use third party web analytics tools to capture information about your use of the Site, such as mouse clicks and scrolling activity. For example, we may use Google Analytics, Google Website Optimizer, or Segment. The providers of these tools may capture data about your activity on our Site, via cookies and other techniques.

 **Information You Submit.**  
We may ask you to volunteer information about yourself using the Site. For example, we may ask you to provide your name, phone number, and email address, demographic data (such as your profession, age, gender, interests), and information about your general interest in the Service. Your submission of this type of information as a guest on the Site is not required.

 **Links from Other Sites.**  
If you arrive at our site by clicking on an advertisement or content published by a third party, that third party may provide information to us about your activity on their site. For example, we may use Google AdWords or other third party advertisers, or may sponsor links on other third party sites.

 **Data Services.**  
We may have data about you that we purchased from third party “data matching” services. A data matching service combines data from multiple website operators and uses automated techniques to match data collected from various places to a single individual. Please see the section below captioned Online Behavioral Advertising to learn about behavior advertising practices or to opt out of this type of advertising.

 **Combination with Other Data.**  
If you register for our Services, we may combine information we collect about you as a Site guest with the information we collect about you as a Service user, including personally identifying information, such as your name.

### How do we use your personal information?

Any of the information we collect from or about you may be used in one of the following ways:

 **To improve our website**  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

 **To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**

 **To send periodic emails**  
Any email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to our services, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, reply to the email with the subject line ‘Unsubscribe’ to be removed from future emails.

Filestack only uses and processes personal data for purposes compatible with the original purpose of collection or as subsequently authorized by you.

### How do we protect your information?

We use industry standard and reasonable measures to protect the security of your personal data.

### Online Data Collection Technologies?

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies in order to implement authentication and to enable core features of our application, as well as to enable us to better understand user behavior. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. However, if you turn your cookies off, most of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information except as follows:

  * To trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
  * When we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. We also may be required to disclose an individual’s personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

In addition, if we ever decide to sell our business we may provide the information to a potential acquirer but only to the extent customary in these circumstances and subject to the potential acquirer’s agreement to maintain the information in confidence and use it only for the purpose of evaluating the potential acquisition.

We provide non-personally identifiable visitor information to others for marketing, advertising, or other uses. In limited circumstances we permit these third parties to further share this non-personally identifiable information with others for the purpose of assisting others in developing their online advertising and marketing strategies. For example, we may permit a data service to associate the de-identified data we provide with other information it may have about you. The data service would then use the combined data to provide data services to other website operators and advertisers to assist them in more effectively targeting their content and advertising. Please see the section below captioned Online Behavioral Advertising to learn about behavioral advertising practices or to opt out of this type of advertising.

We will provide an individual opt-out or opt-in choice before we share your data with third parties other than as described above, or before we use it for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized.

Filestack’s accountability for personal data that it receives under the EU- US Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party is described in the Privacy Shield Principles. In particular, Filestack remains responsible and liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if third-party agents that it engages to process the personal data on its behalf do so in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless Filestack proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not intentionally collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Data Integrity

Filestack processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage, and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store, and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

### Privacy Shield

Filestack complies with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Frameworks as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Filestack has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

  * In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Filestack commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact us at: [privacy@filestack.com.](mailto:privacy@filestack.com)
  * Filestack has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. Data subjects in the EU and in Switzerland who do not receive timely acknowledgment of their complaint, or fee that their complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, should visit <https://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/> for more information and to file a complaint.  The services of the Better Business Bureau are provided at no cost to you.
  * Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.

### Enforcement

Filestack regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or Filestack’s treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site or by writing to us at Your Privacy Rights, c/o Filestack, 122 E. Houston, 2nd Floor, San Antonio, TX 78205. When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is Filestack’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Filestack and an individual.

The U.S. Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction to investigate and enforce Filestack’s compliance with Privacy Shield requirements.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline or information that we receive from our customers as part of providing services.

### Online Behavioral Advertising

To learn more about behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at www.aboutads.info or Networking Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) choices.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on November 8, 2017.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Filestack  
122 E. Houston St, 2nd Floor  
San Antonio, TX 78205
